music-sharing.net 2005-04-06

# MP3SHARINGCENTER

**MP3SHARINGCENTER.COM**

**PRIVACY POLICY**

**Welcome to Mp3SharingCenter.com (the "Site").**

We understand that privacy online is important to users of our Site, especially when conducting business. 

This statement governs our privacy policies with respect to those users of the Site ("Visitors") who visit without 

Transacting business and Visitors who register to transact business on the Site and make use of the various services offered by Mp3SharingCenter.com (collectively, "Services") ("Authorized Customers").

**Personally Identifiable Information**

Refers to any information that identifies or can be used to identify, contact, or locate the person, to whom such information pertains, including, but not limited to, name, address, phone number, fax number, email address, financial profiles, social security number, and credit card information. Personally Identifiable Information does not include information that is collected anonymously (that is, without identification of the individual user) 

or demographic information not connected to an identified individual.

**What Personally Identifiable Information is collected?**

We may collect basic user profile information from all of our Visitors. We collect the following additional information from our Authorized Customers: the names, addresses, phone numbers and email addresses.

**How does the Site use Personally Identifiable Information?**

We use Personally Identifiable Information to customize the Site, to make appropriate service offerings, and to fulfill buying and selling requests on the Site. We may email Visitors and Authorized Customers about research or purchase and selling opportunities on the Site or information related to the subject matter of the Site. We may also use Personally Identifiable Information to contact Visitors and Authorized Customers in response to specific inquiries, or to provide requested information. 

**How is Personally Identifiable Information stored?**

Personally Identifiable Information collected by Mp3SharingCenter.com is securely stored and is not accessible to third parties or employees of Mp3SharingCenter.com

**Are Cookies Used on the Site?**

Cookies are used for a variety of reasons. We use Cookies to obtain information about the preferences of our Visitors and the services they select. We also use Cookies for security purposes to protect our Authorized Customers. For example, if an Authorized Customer is logged on and the site is unused for more than 10 minutes, we will automatically log the Authorized Customer off.

**How does Mp3SharingCenter.com use login information?**

Mp3SharingCenter.com uses login information, including, but not limited to, IP addresses, ISPs, and browser types, to analyze trends, administer the Site, track a user's movement and use, and gather broad demographic information.

**How can Visitors correct any inaccuracies in Personally Identifiable Information?**

Visitors and Authorized Customers may contact us to update Personally Identifiable Information about them or to correct any inaccuracies by emailing us at webmaster@Mp3SharingCenter.com 

**What happens if the Privacy Policy Changes?**

We will let our Visitors and Authorized Customers know about changes to our privacy policy by posting such changes on the Site. However, if we are changing our privacy policy in a manner that might cause disclosure of Personally Identifiable Information that a Visitor or Authorized Customer has previously requested not be disclosed, we will contact such Visitor or Authorized Customer to allow such Visitor or Authorized Customer to prevent such disclosure. 

**Links:**

This web site contains links to other web sites. Please note that when you click on one of these links, you are moving to another web site. We encourage you to read the privacy statements of these linked sites as their privacy policies may differ from ours. 

© 2005 Mp3SharingCenter.com , All rights reserved.

Unauthorized duplication or publication of any materials from this Site is expressly prohibited.
